(Amy:)Hey, boyfriend.
(Sheldon:)Can't talk. Spitball.
(Sheldon:)Probably gonna die.
(gargling)
(Sheldon:)Well?
Sheldon, I-I promise.
(Leonard:)Your uvula does not have an STD.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
(Sheldon:)It just doesn't feel as
innocent as it used to.
(Howard:)You reported me
to human resources?
(Sheldon:)You violated the sanctity
of my mouth.
(Howard:)Well, I dropped your class,
so I hope you're happy.
(Sheldon:)I told you you weren't
smart enough to take it.
(Howard:)I'm smart enough, Sheldon.
(Howard:)Asking me a bunch of questions
(Howard:)about a topic
I'm not familiar with
(Howard:)doesn't prove anything.
(Howard:)I could do the same to you.
(Sheldon:)Yeah... Try me.
(Penny:)Okay.
(scoffs)
(Howard:)You enjoy making fun
of engineering so much;